I'm Peppa Pig!
[oinks]
This is my little brother George.
This is Mommy Pig.
[oinks]
And this is Daddy Pig.
[oinks loudly then all laugh]
Peppa Pig!
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] Peppa's family are on holiday
in their Camper Van.
[rooster crowing]
[Daddy Pig]
Good morning, my little piggies!
[all] Good morning, Daddy Pig!
I love camping!
Since we're in the countryside,
I thought we could spend the day
looking at nature.
Good idea, Mommy Pig!
Let's watch a nature program.
[announcer]
One of the wonders of nature, birds.
How lovely!
[cawing]
Shoosh! Shoosh, little birdie!
We can't hear our TV.
Oh, Daddy Pig!
There's no point
being on a camping holiday
and just watching TV.
We can do that at home!
Uh, good thinking, Mommy Pig.
There are lots of fun places we can visit.
There's Tree World.
What's Tree World?
Tree World is a big forest, full of trees.
It sounds a bit boring.
Or there's Potato City.
What's Potato City?
There's a tour of the potato fields,
ending with a potato tasting.
Sounds interesting!
Or there's Duck Land.
What's Duck Land?
It's a wide river, full of ducks.
Duck Land!
Let's go to Duck Land!
[oinks]
[narrator]
Peppa and George love ducks.
How do we get to Duck Land?
The Camper Van can guide us.
[female voice]
Hello. Where are we going today?
Duck Land, please!
[female voice]
Follow the road ahead in a straight line.
[all singing] We're going to Duck Land
In our Camper Van
Welcome to Duck Land!
-How many tickets, please?
-Two adults and two children.
Enjoy the ducks!
Where are the ducks?
Maybe they're on holiday.
Let's have our picnic lunch!
-The ducks always turn up--
-When we have picnics!
[laughing]
[narrator]
Peppa and George love picnics.
[ducks quacking]
Look! It's the ducks!
Stop, Daddy! We need bread for the ducks!
Huh? Oh, heh.
All right!
Hello, Mrs. Duck!
[narrator] Here come more ducks.
All their brothers and sisters are here!
[narrator] And here come more ducks!
It's the Granny and Grandpa ducks!
And here are all the Aunties and Uncles!
[all quacking]
That's the last of our picnic gone!
Ducks, say thank you to Daddy Pig!
Oh, ho! You're most welcome!
Ha-ha-ha! I love Duck Land!
[narrator] It is time to go home.
I wonder what's the shortest way home.
[female voice]
Drive straight ahead into the river.
Oh! Are you sure?
[female voice] Yes. Drive into the river.
But we can't drive in a river!
Yes. It's talking nonsense!
[female voice]
Please press the blue button.
[narrator]
The Camper Van is driving into the river!
Our Camper Van has turned into a boat!
I wasn't quite expecting that.
[female voice]
Welcome to the car of the future.
Look! It's Granddad Dog and Danny Dog!
Ahoy there, Daddy Pig!
[honking]
Uh... Ahoy there!
Sailing on the river
In our camper van
[female voice] Drive up the next hill.
You have reached your destination.
We're home!
Thank you for a lovely holiday,
Mrs. Camper Van.
[female voice]
Ho, ho! You're most welcome.
It's nice going on holiday.
But it's nicer to be back
in our own little house!
[Daddy Pig] Good night, my little piggies!
[Peppa] Good night!
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] Daddy Pig is making
vegetable soup for lunch.
Daddy, can I help?
Thank you, Peppa. Can you clear away
all these vegetable peelings?
Okay! Ha-ha-ha.
[Mommy Pig] Stop, Peppa!
Vegetable peelings don't go
in the normal bin.
They go in this brown bin.
Ooh, na-na.
That's right, George. It's a banana skin.
And there are onions and carrots
and all sorts fruit
and vegetable leftovers in here.
Granny and Grandpa will like these.
Do Granny and Grandpa Pig
eat potato peelings?
Ha-ha-ha. No, Peppa.
They're for Grandpa's garden.
They help his plants grow.
-We'll take these round there after lunch.
-Oh, goody!
[narrator] Mommy Pig, Peppa,
and George are taking the peelings
over to Granny and Grandpa Pig's house.
We're here!
Hooray!
-Grandpa Pig!
-Baba Ig!
We've got a special present for you.
Ah! Vegetable peelings!
Fantastic!
My garden will like these.
Does your garden eat vegetables?
Ha, ha. No, Peppa, these peelings
are for my compost heap.
What's that?
I'll show you.
Here it is.
It's a wooden box!
Yes, Peppa,
but it's a very clever wooden box.
I put these peelings in the top,
and then out of the bottom comes
lovely rich earth called compost.
How does it do that?
Is it a magic box?
[laughs]
No, Peppa.
I've got some little friends
that give it some help.
Where?
In here. Look.
Ah! Wriggly worms.
Wiggle wiggle.
[narrator] The worms turn all the fruit
and vegetables into compost.
Grandpa, can we find some more
wriggly worms for your compost heap?
What a good idea.
Come on, George!
Let's find some more wriggly worms.
[laughing]
A wriggly worm!
Wiggle wiggle!
You're a wriggly worm
How do you do?
I love you
You're a wriggly worm
Ah-ha! Well done!
Be a good wriggly worm,
and turn it all into compost!
[all laugh]
Then I can use the compost to--
I know! I know!
You put a seed in the ground,
cover it in compost,
and it grows into a tree.
Yes, Peppa!
And talking of trees,
we'd better go and help Granny Pig.
She's collecting fruit in the orchard.
What's the orchard?
It's where you find fruit trees.
We've had this orchard
since I was a little piggy.
-Hello, Granny Pig.
-Gangy Ig!
-Are you going to help me collect apples?
-Yes, Granny!
Oh. The apples are too high up.
Don't worry, Peppa.
Granny and Grandpa have
a little trick to collect the apples.
Everybody hold onto the tree.
On the count of three,
shake the tree as much as you can.
One, two, three!
It's raining apples!
[laughs]
Granny, can we have an apple, please?
Of course, Peppa.
Delicious!
And can you guess what we do
with the apple cores?
Uh...
-Wiggle wiggle!
-[narrator] That's right!
The apple cores go into the compost
for the worms.
Clever George!
And clever wriggly worms, too!
[all laughing]
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] Peppa and George
are playing in their bedroom.
This will be the best house ever!
[laughing]
[door bell rings]
[Daddy Pig]
George! Richard Rabbit is here!
-Georgie!
-Richard!
-Dine-Saw!
Bye-bye, Richard.
I'll be back to pick you up later.
[narrator]
George and Richard are friends.
[laughing]
George! Richard!
You've knocked my house down!
Please play something not bouncy.
[narrator] George has made the toy basket
into a volcano!
Richard is using toy trees
to make a jungle!
George has used the building blocks
to make a river!
-Dine-Saw!
[narrator] George and Richard have turned
the bedroom into Dinosaur Land!
I'm leaving! It's too noisy!
-I say Po-tay-to
-And I say Po-tah-to
-Po-tay-to
-Po-tah-to
The good thing about rainy days is
we get to watch important TV programs.
-Po-tay-to!
-Po-tah-to!
Mummy, George and Richard have
made the bedroom into Dinosaur Land.
And Dinosaur Land is very noisy.
George has his best friend here,
but I've got no one to play with.
You could ask Suzy Sheep to come over.
[narrator]
Suzy Sheep is Peppa's best friend.
Can Suzy really come over now?
Let's ring her.
[ringing]
Hello, Suzy Sheep speaking.
Suzy, it's me.
Can you come to my house now?
Yes, Peppa! Can I wear my nurse's costume?
Yes, but come quickly.
-Bye-bye, Suzy! I'll be back to...
-Quick, Suzy!
...pick you up later.
George! Richard!
Nurse Suzy is here.
And Nurse Suzy says,
this is not Dinosaur Land.
It is a hospital.
And a hospital must be clean and tidy.
[narrator]
The bedroom is not Dinosaur Land anymore.
It is a hospital.
I'm the important doctor.
Mm. This dinosaur looks sick.
I agree, doctor.
He is a very greeny ill color.
He must go to bed.
And this dinosaur
is a very purple-y ill color.
Yes, doctor. He must go into bed, too.
-Dine-Saw!
Shush. Quiet in the hospital!
Choo! Choo!
[narrator]
The bedroom is not a hospital anymore.
Now it is a railway station.
No! No!
There aren't any trains in Fairy Land!
[narrator]
Oh. Now the bedroom is Fairy Land.
Only pretty things are allowed
in Fairy Land.
[crying]
What's all this crying about?
George and Richard
want to play dinosaurs and trains.
And we want to play hospitals and fairies.
Mm. I see the rain has stopped outside.
-So?
-So, maybe you could all play outside.
But they like little boys' games.
And we like grown-up girls' games.
But after it's been raining in the garden,
what do you normally find?
-Muddy...
-Puddles!
And what are muddy puddles for?
Jumping up and down in!
[narrator] Everyone loves jumping
up and down in muddy puddles.
Whether they are big girls or little boys.
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] It has been very stormy
weather, and the school roof is leaking.
How can we raise the money
to fix the school roof?
We could have a fun run!
What's a funny run?
It's a day for picnics
and giving money to see people run.
And the more money you give,
the further they run.
Good idea, Daddy Pig.
How far can you run?
What? Uh...
Well, I can run as far as you like.
But, Daddy, you can hardly run at all!
Nonsense!
-I'm an expert at running.
-Good.
-Does anyone else want to run?
-No, thank you.
But I'll give money to see Daddy Pig run!
-Me, too!
-And me!
Excellent! Thank you, Daddy Pig!
[narrator]
Peppa and her family are eating spaghetti.
Delicious! Is there any more spaghetti?
Daddy Pig!
You've already had three helpings!
Eating gives me energy.
And I need energy for my fun run!
You also need to practice running!
What if I practice eating today,
then practice running tomorrow?
No, Daddy!
You need to practice running now!
-Oh.
-Come on, Daddy, race you!
This is easy!
[narrator]
It is easy to run downhill.
It is hard to run uphill.
I don't think I should have eaten
so much spaghetti.
[bell ringing]
[narrator]
It is the day of the fun run.
Madame Gazelle has a chart
to show how far Daddy Pig must run.
If Daddy Pig can run to here...
The supermarket!
...then to here...
My Granddad's garage!
...and all the way to here...
Windy Castle!
...then we'll have enough money
to fix the school roof!
I'll do it now.
Ready, steady, go!
I did it! Now we can have the picnic!
Ha, ha. Silly Daddy!
That's just a drawing.
Yes. Now you must run
to the real Windy Castle.
Oh.
-Ready, steady, go!
-Hooray!
Huff, puff, huff, puff.
Come on, Daddy Pig, you can make it!
Come on, bus, you can make it!
[narrator] The school bus has made it
to Windy Castle.
Now everyone can enjoy the picnic.
Water! Water!
What a lovely hot day.
And such a relaxing way
to raise money, too.
Water! Water!
[narrator]
Daddy Pig has reached the Supermarket.
All the running has made him very thirsty.
Let's look through the telescope!
I can see Daddy!
[narrator] The telescope
makes everything look closer.
[Peppa] Oh, he's not going very fast.
[narrator] Daddy Pig has arrived
at Granddad Dog's garage.
That's it. I can't go on.
Daddy has stopped!
[all] Aww.
You look rather hot.
You need something to cool you down
and give you energy.
Have an ice lolly!
Thank you, Granddad Dog!
That's nice!
Aah! A wasp!
Shoo! Shoo! Get away, you little pest!
[narrator] The wasp wants to share
Daddy Pig's ice lolly.
No! This is my lolly.
Daddy's started running again,
really fast!
Hooray!
[screaming]
Get off! Get off!
You can stop now, Daddy Pig!
We have enough money
to fix the school roof!
[screaming]
[narrator]
Daddy Pig has lost the wasp.
Well done, Daddy Pig!
All that extra running means
we've got enough money
for a new school bus, too!
Thank you, Daddy Pig!
Oh? Oh.
You're most welcome.
[all laughing]
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] Daddy Pig is doing the washing
this morning.
Daddy, what's that shirt?
It's my football shirt.
Daddy's playing football this afternoon.
Ooh.
But first, I have to go to work.
-See you later! Bye.
-Bye-bye.
Poor Daddy. Having to go to work.
Ah. Poor Daddy.
Come on, let's play!
Yes, let's play.
[narrator] Peppa loves jumping up and down
in muddy puddles.
George loves jumping up and down
Mommy Pig loves jumping up and down
in muddy puddles!
Oh, dear.
Mommy! We've splashed
Daddy's football shirt with mud!
Don't worry. We'll just wash it.
[laughs]
It'll be washed in no time,
and Daddy won't know it was ever muddy.
Let's find some more things
to put in the machine.
Oh, my dress is a bit muddy.
[narrator] Mommy Pig and George
have found more things to wash.
Very good, George.
We put the clothes in here...
and then, we switch it on.
[narrator] The washing machine
is filling up with hot soapy water.
Splosh, splosh, splosh.
[narrator] The washing machine
is making the whole room shake!
Oh, Peppa, where's your dress?
I'm washing it!
What?
Oh, no!
Look, Mummy,
my red dress is all nice and clean.
Yes, Peppa, but look what it's done
to everything else!
[narrator] Oh, dear!
Peppa's red dress
has made all the white clothes pink!
Pink isn't a very good color
for a football shirt.
Ooh.
[narrator] Daddy Pig is home from work.
Hello, everyone!
Hello, Daddy.
Uh, Daddy Pig, we've got
a bit of a problem, and...
Tell me later, Mommy Pig.
I've got to get ready for football.
-Now, where's my football shirt?
-Here.
Don't be silly, Peppa.
That's one of Mummy's dresses.
It's pink!
No, Daddy. It's your football shirt.
It got a bit muddy.
So, we washed it.
And it all went a bit wrong.
Sorry, Daddy.
But I can't wear a pink football shirt!
Why not, Daddy? Pink is a lovely color!
Hmm.
-What do you think, George?
-Yuck!
[narrator] George does not like pink!
[door bell rings]
[narrator] Here are Daddy Pig's friends,
Mr. Bull, Mr. Rabbit,
Mr. Pony, and Mr. Zebra.
Moo!
Is Daddy Pig coming out to play?
He'll just be a moment.
My team are in white.
I need a white shirt!
But, Daddy, you have a white shirt.
Just take off your jacket.
-See?
-Fantastic!
Thank you, Peppa.
-Hello, everyone.
-Hello, Daddy Pig.
-Like your shirt.
-Very smart!
Thank you. Come on! Let's play football!
Yes!
-Goal!
-Hooray!
-Daddy!
You've made your shirt all muddy!
Ha-ha-ha. Of course, Peppa!
Football shirts are meant to be muddy!
[oinks loudly then Peppa laughs]
[narrator]
Daddy Pig loves playing football.
Everyone loves playing football.
Especially when its muddy.
[all laughing]